# Jo Wimborne

19 St Margaret's Court, Linnet Close, Cardiff 07772 207511 • jowimborne@gmail.com joalfie.github.io

I am a front-end turned full-stack developer who enjoys learning new things, building cool stuff and playing with swords. Though I have studied and worked in various fields over the past five years, my consistent goal throughout has been to put in as much as I can to every experience and take every opportunity to learn. I am enthusiastic and creative with a keen attention to detail, and I enjoy sharing this with other people. I enjoy a challenge and a working experience which has something different every day, particularly with a strong team of colleagues which I can contribute to.

# **Employment**

## Orchard Media & Events, Cardiff: web developer

June 2017 - Present

- Taking designs produced by graphic designers and turning them into clean, semantic code for responsive websites, with considerations of user experience, performance, accessibility and security.
- Adapting to, and challenging when necessary, client requirements and deadlines.
- Working with other developers using version control (Git).
- Using CMSs (Symphony, WordPress, Prismic.io) to create easy to understand 'back ends' for clients to be able to update their websites, and for creating site pages through templating in XSLT, PHP and Pug.
- Learning new skills and tools and putting them into practice in projects, for example I learned React Native and have since been responsible for building and deploying three apps to Google Play Store and Apple App Store.
- Communicating with clients via email, phone calls and in-person meetings.
- Basic server and web hosting management, including updating PHP versions and handling a mass transferring of sites to a new server.

#### Edel Fencing Academy: admin, social media, assistant instructor

March 2016 - Present

- Administration tasks including printing, organising and storing waivers (in accordance with GDPR), taking membership payments and organising insurance and venue bookings.
- Keeping an active social media presence, and handling enquiries through social media and email.
- Being responsible for a full rebrand, including logo design, merchandise orders, and an upcoming website.
- Organising and teaching workshops and classes to groups of up to 20 students, both in the club (including three successful 8-week beginners courses) and at national events (including the May Melee 2019). I have also been invited to teach at the world's biggest HEMA event for women and gender minorities next year (By the Sword 2020).
- As a member of both the EFA and Wessex League committees I am involved in regular work to improve access to HEMA, welfare within the community, and organisation of events, including helping to host a tournament in Cardiff with up to 100 participants.

## **Sherman Theatre Cafe Bar, Cardiff: bartender and other FOH roles**

April 2016 - June 2017

#### Old Market Tavern (formerly O'Neills), Cardiff: bartender and waitress

September 2014 - November 2015

# **Education**

September 2013 – June 2017	University of South Wales, Cardiff Campus	BA (Hons) Graphic Communication 2:1
2011 – 2013	Lancaster Girls' Grammar School Sixth Form	A Levels grade AAA*